box8.in 2014-12-05

# BOX8

##  Privacy Policy 

Your IP is logged when placing an order. This is for reasons of fraud protection. Fraudulent orders will be submitted to the appropriate authorities 

In general, you can visit this Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors.

BOX8 collect personal information from you including your first and last name, address, telephone and mobile number(s), email address and any other information, when you knowingly provide us with this information. This will generally occur when you either:

  * Visit Online ordering site to place order;
  * enter into a competition or promotion;
  * participate in a survey;
  * subscribe to our mailing list;
  * apply for a job;
  * submit website feedback;

Where ever BOX8 collects personal information about you from someone else, BOX8 will take reasonable steps to advise you. 

### Use and Disclosure

Except as otherwise stated, we may use information collected via this site to improve the content of our site, to customize the site to your preferences, to communicate information to you, and for any other purpose specified.

BOX8may use the personal information that you submit to store and process that information in order to provide goods and services. Generally, we may use your personal information in the ways in which you would expect, including but not limited, to any of the following purposes:

  * to process any job application you may submit;
  * To provide you with any restaurant or promotion information;
  * To process any online ordering;
  * To determine the number of visitors to our websites and conduct reviews of our sites
  * To fulfill prizes, awards and purchases;
  * To respond to specific requests from visitors;
  * To keep you informed about any changes to our websites;
  * To conduct marketing research; and
  * To now and again send you offers or information on products or services that we consider will be of interest to you.

Further information on how we use your personal information when using our Internet ordering system 

When using the BOX8 internet ordering system additional information is collected when you order online. This information assists in the delivery to your door and to verify your credentials. The internet order system also stores information about your order to help you remember and re-order the same menu in future. When concluding your order via the BOX8 internet ordering system, you will be asked if you would like to associate your mobile number with social media such as Facebook or yahoo. You may choose to do that for ease of ordering when you come next time.

### Credit Card Details

BOX8 does not store any of your credit card details 

### Third Party Disclosure

Personal information that you submit to BOX8’s may be disclosed to a third party: 

Such as our suppliers, as mailing houses, who are employed to provide some of our services such; to meet the purpose for which it was submitted; 

  * If you have provided your express consent to share the information;
  * If BOX8 is required or authorized by law to disclose the information;
  * If you’re personal information is collected in connection with a joint promoter, to that joint promoter for marketing and research purposes;
  * If BOX8 feel you might like to know about a third party's goods and services we may supply that personal information to that third party. (We know that many of our guests enjoy receiving these excellent offers);

### Access, Accuracy and Security

BOX8 will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information collected is accurate, complete and up-to-date.

You can access and request correction of any personal information concerning you at any time. You may also request that your personal information be deleted at any time. Any such requests should be made directly by contacting us.

BOX8 will take reasonable steps to protect personal information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.

### Sensitive Information

BOX8 will not collect, use or disclose sensitive information except with your specific consent.

### Click stream Data

Each time you visit the BOX8’s site our server collects some anonymous information, known as click- stream data, including the type of browser and system you are using; the address of the site you have come from and move to after your visit; the date and time of your visit; and your server's IP address. BOX8’smay collect this information for statistical purposes to find out how the websites is used and navigated, including the number of hits, the frequency and duration of visits, most popular session times. Poncho Hospitality Pvt. Ltd. may use this information to evaluate and improve the BOX8 websites.

### Cookies

A Cookie is a piece of information that our web server may send to your machine when you visit a BOX8’ssite. A Cookie helps us to recognize you when you re-visit our sites and to co-ordinate your access to different pages on the sites.

### Changes

If this Privacy Policy is changed, the revised policy will be posted on this site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information. 

### Consent

By using this site, you agree to the terms of the policy as stated above. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of the information in accordance with the Privacy Policy of Poncho Hospitality Ltd
